Jesus made a promise that I think much of the church has forgotten.
Jesus said, you will not see me
again until you say, blessed is the one who comes in the name of the Lord.
Welcome to Life is your word episode five.
in this show, we build out our understanding of reality by seeking God's
face first. Today's reading is from Luke chapter 13. Jesus went through
town and village after another teaching on his way to Jerusalem. Someone
asked him, Lord, will only a few be saved? He
said to them,
strive to enter through the narrow door. For many I
tell you, will try to enter and we'll not be able.
There will be weeping and gnashing of teeth,
when you see Abraham and Isaac and Jacob
and all the prophets in the kingdom of God,
and you yourselves thrown out,
then people from east and west, north and south, will take their
places at the banquet in the kingdom of God. Indeed, some more first will be
last.
Indeed, some, indeed, some,
forget that verse. At that very
hour, some Pharisees came out and said to him, get away
from here, for Herod wants to kill you.
Jesus weeped, saying Jerusalem, the city that
kills the prophets, and stones those who are sent
to it.
How often I have desired to gather
your children together as a hen her brood
under her wings, and you were not
willing. and I tell you, you will not see me again
until you say, blessed is the one who comes
in the name of the Lord. When we learn how to say, Blessed is the one who comes in
the name of the Lord, rather than to bicker about what. If you want to know
whether or not you follow the true God, ask yourself the following
question. When you look at somebody like me, will you be able to
say, blessed is the one who comes in the name of the Lord to me or not?
That will tell you a whole lot about the kind of person that you are and
whether or not the Holy Spirit truly lives in you. there are many who
have gone out of their way to hate on me.
There are those who have actually kicked me out of churches
simply because I'm different.
That's not God.
Jesus has asked us to grow as His
people into something new to evolve into what
He has truly called us to be.
Those who instead of looking on the outside as humans
do, look at the inside to the heart and say, is the
Lord with this person? Does this person come in the name
of the Lord? Because if they do, I want to make sure that I bless them.
Now that is what Christ's likeness is. And Jesus promised that we won't
see Him again until we all start saying that.
So that is my ask today.
Instead of asking why is somebody doing that
I might want to call a sin or not?
You ask yourself the question,
how can I bless those who say that they come in the
name of the Lord? In love and unity Asabaal. How has God taught
you to bless those that come in His name? Share your revelations in the comments
below.